Guide to the Liederkranz Collection ca. 1847-1987 MSS.130
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Printed Sheet Music Collection
  - Composer: Scharwenka, Xaver Title: Mataswintha Uniform Title: Mataswintha. Selection Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Ch.B.507., undated (Box 166, Folder 2849)
  - Composer: Scharwenka, Xaver Title: Polish National Dance Uniform Title: Polnische Tanze, op. 3; arr Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 1593-28, undated (Box 63, Folder 807)
  - Composer: Scharwenka, Xaver Title: Polnischer Nationaltanz, op. 3, no. 1 Uniform Title: Polnische Tanze, op. 3; arr Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.654., undated (Box 63, Folder 808)
  - Composer: Schiebold, Carl Title: Madel, schenk' ein! Uniform Title: Madel, schenk' ein! Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Ernst Eulenberg Plate Number: E. E. 4371, undated (Box 167, Folder 2875)
  - Composer: Schild, F. Title: The Band's Coming. March Uniform Title: D'Band Kommt Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 1755-18, undated (Box 123, Folder 1777)
  - Composer: Schiller, Carl Title: O traume nur! Uniform Title: O traume nur! Publisher information: Coburg (Germany): C. Schiller (Engelmann & Muhlberg, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: C. S. 2 Engraver: Engelmann & Muhlberg, Leipzig, undated (Box 168, Folder 2904)
  - Composer: Schjelderup, Gerhard, arr. Title: Sonntag auf der Alm Uniform Title: Pa Solen jeg ser Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel's Musikalienhandlung (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 14735 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 172, Folder 3096)
  - Composer: Schlesinger, L. Title: Un Modele Uniform Title: Modele Plate Number: L. S. 4., undated (Box 63, Folder 810)
  - Composer: Schlesinger, Sebastian B. Title: Auf Wiederseh'n! Uniform Title: Auf Wiederseh'n!, undated (Box 124, Folder 1790)
  - Composer: Schmelz, R. Title: Wilkommen zu Heinrich Zollner Uniform Title: Wilkommen zu Heinrich Zollner, undated (Box 111, Folder 1590)
  - Composer: Schmelz, Reinhard Title: Fruhlingsglaube Uniform Title: Fruhlingsglaube Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Schlesinger Buch- & Musikhandlung Plate Number: S. 8258, undated (Box 158, Folder 2524)
  - Composer: Schmelz, Reinhard Title: Traumerei Uniform Title: Traumerei Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Friedrich Luckhardt (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 433 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 96, Folder 1195)
  - Composer: Schmelz, Reinhard Title: Traumerei Uniform Title: Traumerei Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Friedrich Luckhardt (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. L. 384 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 96, Folder 1196)
  - Composer: Schmid, Fr. J., arr. Title: Zweiundvierzig Soloquartette fur Mannerstimmen Uniform Title: Zweiundvierzig Soloquartette fur Mannerstimmen Publisher information: Freising (Germany): Franz Paul Datterer Plate Number: 2, undated (Box 174, Folder 3227)
  - Composer: Schmidt, C. J. Title: Gothenzug Uniform Title: Gothenzug Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 22243-3, undated (Box 162, Folder 2690)
  - Composer: Schmidt, C. J. Title: Gothenzug Uniform Title: Gothenzug Publisher information: New York: Edward Schuberth & Co. Plate Number: E. S. & Co. 3103, undated (Box 162, Folder 2689)
  - Composer: Schmidt, C. J. Title: Gothenzug Uniform Title: Gothenzug Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 15987, undated (Box 162, Folder 2691)
  - Composer: Schmidt, Gustav Title: Carmosenella Uniform Title: Carmosenella Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Robert Forberg (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 2677. Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 162, Folder 2694)
  - Composer: Schmidt, Gustave Title: Alibi. Komische Operette Uniform Title: Alibi Publisher information: Hamburg (Germany): Hugo Pohle (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: H. P. 523 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 79, Folder 1021)
  - Composer: Schmitt, Jacques Title: Quatre Etudes de Concert. No. 4. Etude de Chant Uniform Title: Quatre Etudes de Concert, op. 330, no. 4. Etude de Chant Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Schuberth & Co. (F. W. Garbrecht, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 1223 Engraver: F. W. Garbrecht, Leipzig, undated (Box 99, Folder 1272)
  - Composer: Schmoll, A. Title: Cymbals and Castanets. Caprice Espagnol Uniform Title: Cymbals and Castanets. Caprice Espagnol Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 11914, undated (Box 102, Folder 1327)
  - Composer: Schmolzer, Jakob Eduard Title: Die Waldfee Uniform Title: Waldfee Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel's Musikalienhandlung (E. Jul. Pickenhahn, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 5769, undated (Box 173, Folder 3173)
  - Composer: Schneider, H. J. Title: Bienenhaus Marsch Uniform Title: Bienenhaus Publisher information: Prague (Czech Republic): Joh. Hoffmann Plate Number: 4419, undated (Box 110, Folder 1580)
  - Composer: Schneider, H. J. Title: The Bee Hive Uniform Title: Bienenhaus; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 5066-17, undated (Box 110, Folder 1581)
  - Composer: Scholz, Bernhard Title: Das Siegesfest Uniform Title: Siegesfest Publisher information: Mainz (Germany): B. Schott's Söhne Plate Number: 23782., undated (Box 98, Folder 1232)
  - Composer: Scholz, Bernhard Title: Standchen an eine Verlassene Uniform Title: Standchen an eine Verlassene Publisher information: Breslau (Germany): Julius Hainauer (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: J. 2593 H. Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 100, Folder 1303)
  - Composer: Schonberger, John, Richard Coburn and Vincent Rose Title: Whispering Uniform Title: Whispering Publisher information: New York: Miller Music Corporation Plate Number: 491-2, undated (Box 145, Folder 2030)
  - Composer: Schrammel, Johann Title: Wien bleibt Wien! Uniform Title: Wien bleibt Wien! Publisher information: Hamburg (Germany): August Cranz Plate Number: C. 27235., undated (Box 122, Folder 1761)
  - Composer: Schrammel, Johann Title: Wien bleibt Wien Uniform Title: Wien bleibt Wien Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 2519-5, undated (Box 103, Folder 1375)
  - Composer: Schrattenholz, Leo Title: Meine Gottin Uniform Title: Meine Gottin Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock Plate Number: 11165, undated (Box 125, Folder 1810)
  - Composer: Schreck, Gust. E. Title: Lauf der Welt Uniform Title: Lauf der Welt Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 6236-3, undated (Box 165, Folder 2801)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Abendfrieden Uniform Title: Abendfrieden; arr., undated (Box 173, Folder 3160)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Alphonso and Estrella. Overture Uniform Title: Alphonso und Estrella. Ouverture; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 7407-49, undated (Box 65, Folder 845)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Alphonso und Estrella. Ouverture Uniform Title: Alphonso und Estrella. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): August Cranz Plate Number: C. 45017, undated (Box 65, Folder 843)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Am Meer Uniform Title: Am Meer; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 2507-35, undated (Box 111, Folder 1593)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Ave Maria Uniform Title: Ave Maria; arr. Publisher information: Mainz (Germany): B. Schott's Söhne Plate Number: 19623, undated (Box 54, Folder 651)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Der Lindenbaum Uniform Title: Lindenbaum, undated (Box 175, Folder 3253)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Der Lindenbaum Uniform Title: Lindenbaum Publisher information: Cologne (Germany): [illegible], undated (Box 173, Folder 3193)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Die Allmacht Uniform Title: Allmacht; arr. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Schuberth & Co. (F. W. Garbrecht [printer]) Plate Number: 4936 Engraver: F. W. Garbrecht, undated (Box 54, Folder 654)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Die Allmacht Uniform Title: Allmacht; arr. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Schuberth & Co. (F. W. Garbrecht [printer]) Plate Number: 4976 Engraver: F. W. Garbrecht, undated (Box 54, Folder 653)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Die Allmacht Uniform Title: Allmacht; arr. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Schuberth & Co. (F. W. Grabrecht [printer]) Plate Number: 4935 Engraver: F. W. Garbrecht, undated (Box 54, Folder 652)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Die Allmacht Uniform Title: Allmacht; arr. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Schuberth & Co. (F. W. Garbrecht [printer]) Plate Number: 4955 Engraver: F. W. Garbrecht, undated (Box 54, Folder 655)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Du bist die Ruh Uniform Title: Du bist die Ruh Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 5960 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 118, Folder 1683)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Du bist die Ruh Uniform Title: Du bist die Ruh Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 5960 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 149, Folder 2155)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Du bist die Ruh Uniform Title: Du bist die Ruh Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 5962 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 118, Folder 1684)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Franz Schubert's Compositionen Uniform Title: Franz Schubert's Compositionen Plate Number: 5417, undated (Box 174, Folder 3220)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Frisch in's Feld Uniform Title: Frisch in's Feld Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: G. H. 896 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 147, Folder 2093)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Geisterchor aus dem drama Rosamunde Uniform Title: Rosamunde. Geisterchor Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): C. A. Spina (A. Eckel [printer]) Plate Number: C.S.18,408, undated (Box 43, Folder 503)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Gesang der Geister uber den Wassern Uniform Title: Gesang der Geister uber den Wassern, D. 714; arr. Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): C. A. Spina Plate Number: C. S. 16, 374. Engraver: A. Grube, Vienna, undated (Box 162, Folder 2677)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Gesang der Geister uber den Wassern Uniform Title: Gesang der Geister uber den Wassern, D. 714 Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): C. A. Spina Plate Number: C. S. 16, 509., undated (Box 54, Folder 659)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Gesang der Geister uber den Wassern Uniform Title: Gesang der Geister uber den Wassern, D. 714 Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): C. A. Spina Plate Number: C. S. 16,373., undated (Box 54, Folder 657)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Gesang der Geister uber den Wassern Uniform Title: Gesang der Geister uber den Wassern, D. 714 Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): C. A. Spina Plate Number: C. S. 18,422., undated (Box 162, Folder 2678)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Gesange fur Mannerchor Uniform Title: Gesange fur Mannerchor Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. Peters Plate Number: 9041 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 79, Folder 1016)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Gott in der Natur Uniform Title: Gott in der Natur; arr. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Rieter-Biedermann (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 810 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 82, Folder 1047)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Gott in der Natur Uniform Title: Gott in der Natur; arr. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Rieter-Biedermann (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 811 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 82, Folder 1048)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Gott in der Natur Uniform Title: Gott in der Natur; arr. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Rieter-Biedermann (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 812 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 82, Folder 1046)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Gott in der Natur Uniform Title: Gott in der Natur; arr. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Rieter-Biedermann (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 813b. Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 82, Folder 1049)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Gott meine Zuversicht Uniform Title: Gott meine Zuversicht Plate Number: 8777., undated (Box 168, Folder 2940)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Gott meine Zuversicht Uniform Title: Gott meine Zuversicht Plate Number: C. 18,414, undated (Box 168, Folder 2939)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Gott meine Zuversicht Uniform Title: Gott meine Zuversicht Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Ernst Eulenberg (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: E. E. 2018 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 168, Folder 2938)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Hymnen Uniform Title: Hymnen, undated (Box 155, Folder 2435)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Marche Militaire Uniform Title: Marches militaires. Nos. 1-2; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 3371-31, undated (Box 54, Folder 658)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Mirjams Siegesgesang Uniform Title: Mirjams Siegesgesang Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bartholf Senff Plate Number: 910, undated (Box 76, Folder 979)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Mirjams Siegesgesang Uniform Title: Mirjams Siegesgesang Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bartholf Senff Plate Number: 911, undated (Box 76, Folder 978)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Mirjams Siegesgesang Uniform Title: Mirjams Siegesgesang Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bartholf Senff Plate Number: 913, undated (Box 76, Folder 977)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Mondenschein Uniform Title: Mondenschein: D. 875, undated (Box 120, Folder 1723)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Mondenschein Uniform Title: Mondenschein: D. 875 Plate Number: D.et C.No.3181, undated (Box 128, Folder 1869)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Nachtgesang im Walde Uniform Title: Nachtgesang im Walde Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): Tobias Haslinger Plate Number: T. H. 10,012, undated (Box 167, Folder 2897)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Nachthelle Uniform Title: Nachthelle Publisher information: Hamburg (Germany): August Cranz Plate Number: C.S.18,415., undated (Box 116, Folder 1659)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Nachthelle Uniform Title: Nachthelle Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): And. Diabelli u. Comp. Plate Number: D. & C. No. 6265, undated (Box 97, Folder 1226)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Ouverture zu dem Drama Rosamunde Uniform Title: Zauberharfe. Ouverture; arr. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Anton J. Benjamin Plate Number: A. J. B. 1974, undated (Box 66, Folder 851)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Ouverture zu Rosamunde Uniform Title: Alphonso und Estrella. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.242., undated (Box 65, Folder 844)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Ouverture zu Rosamunde Uniform Title: Zauberharfe. Ouverture Plate Number: C. 25176., undated (Box 66, Folder 849)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Ouverture zur Oper Rosamunde Uniform Title: Zauberharfe. Ouverture Publisher information: Hamburg (Germany): August Cranz Plate Number: C. S. 19, 102, undated (Box 65, Folder 846)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Ouverture zur Zauberharfe Uniform Title: Zauberharfe. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.241., undated (Box 65, Folder 847)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Ouverture. Rosamunde Uniform Title: Zauberharfe. Ouverture Plate Number: C. S. 10,418., undated (Box 65, Folder 848)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Overture-Rosamunde Uniform Title: Zauberharfe. Ouverture; arr.J. Schott Plate Number: 264-65, undated (Box 66, Folder 852)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Polonaise Uniform Title: Polonaise, op. 61, no. 1; arr. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Rieter-Biedermann Plate Number: 1089a./1089b., undated (Box 54, Folder 660)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Rosamunde. Balletmusik Uniform Title: Rosamunde. Balletmusik Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Orch. B. 655., undated (Box 53, Folder 646)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Rosamunde. Balletmusik Uniform Title: Rosamunde. Balletmusik Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Ernst Eulenberg Plate Number: E. E. 3834, undated (Box 53, Folder 645)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Rosamunde. Ouverture Uniform Title: Rosamunde. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: F.S.187., undated (Box 53, Folder 647)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Rosamunde. Ouverture Uniform Title: Rosamunde. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.242., undated (Box 53, Folder 648)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Rosamunde. Overture Uniform Title: Zauberharfe. Ouverture; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 4994-71, undated (Box 66, Folder 850)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Rosamunde. Zwischenaktmusik Uniform Title: Rosamunde. Zwischenactmusik Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.612., undated (Box 53, Folder 649)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Rosamunde. Zwischenaktmusik Uniform Title: Rosamunde. Zwischenaktmusik; arr. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.612.K., undated (Box 53, Folder 650)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Rosamunde Uniform Title: Rosamunde; arr. Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 34180, undated (Box 175, Folder 3281)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Schubert-Album Uniform Title: Schubert-Album Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. Peters Plate Number: 5366/5494/5495 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 85, Folder 1074)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Schubert-Album Uniform Title: Schubert-Album Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. Peters Plate Number: 5938/39/40/41, 6400/1/2/3, 5475 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 85, Folder 1074)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Serenade Uniform Title: Serenade; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 2507-35, undated (Box 111, Folder 1592)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Serenade Uniform Title: Serenade; arr. Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 12911, undated (Box 104, Folder 1407)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Serenade Uniform Title: Ständchen, D. 920; arr. Publisher information: Cincinnati: The Willis Music Co. Plate Number: 1445-5 1/2, undated (Box 151, Folder 2246)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Serenade Uniform Title: Standchen; arr. Publisher information: Cincinnati: The Willis Music Co. Plate Number: 1445-5 1/2, undated (Box 171, Folder 3063)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Sinfonie in C Dur Uniform Title: Symphony no. 7 [i.e.9], D. 944, C major Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: 6203, undated (Box 63, Folder 812)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Symphonie C dur Uniform Title: Symphony no. 7 [i.e.9], D. 944, C major Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: 7954, undated (Box 63, Folder 811)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Symphonie H moll Uniform Title: Symphony in B minor, D. 759: "Unfinished" Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. Peters Plate Number: 8244 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 64, Folder 817)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Symphonie in H moll (unvollendet) Uniform Title: Symphony in B minor, D. 759: "Unfinished" Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Part.B.154., undated (Box 64, Folder 814)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Symphonie in H moll, No. 8 Uniform Title: Symphony in B minor, D. 759: "Unfinished" Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.133., undated (Box 64, Folder 815)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Symphonie No. 7 Uniform Title: Symphony no. 7 [i.e.9], D. 944, C major Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.131/132, undated (Box 63, Folder 813)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: The Omnipotence Uniform Title: Allmacht; arr. Publisher information: New York: Luckhardt & Belder Plate Number: L & B 3671-7, undated (Box 54, Folder 656)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: The Omnipotence Uniform Title: Allmacht Publisher information: New York: Harold Flammer Incorporated Plate Number: 926, undated (Box 153, Folder 2304)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: The Omnipotence Uniform Title: Allmacht Publisher information: Reading, PA: D. H. van der Stucken, undated (Box 153, Folder 2303)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: To Music Uniform Title: An die Musik; arr. Publisher information: London (Great Britain): Stainer & Bell Ltd. Plate Number: S & B 3786, undated (Box 175, Folder 3267)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: To Music Uniform Title: An die Musik; arr. Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 22000, undated (Box 147, Folder 2100)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Unfinished Symphony Uniform Title: Symphony in B minor, D. 759: "Unfinished"; arr. Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 34043, undated (Box 64, Folder 816)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Unfinished Symphony Uniform Title: Symphony in B minor, D. 759: "Unfinished" Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 4408-84, undated (Box 64, Folder 819)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Unfinished Symphony Uniform Title: Symphony in B minor, D. 759: "Unfinished" Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 34045, undated (Box 64, Folder 821)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Zwei Satze der unvollendeten Sinfonie in H moll Uniform Title: Symphony in B minor, D. 759: "Unfinished" Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): C. A. Spina Plate Number: C.S. 19,165, undated (Box 64, Folder 818)
  - Composer: Schubert, Franz Title: Zwei Satze der unvollendeten Sinfonie Uniform Title: Symphony in B minor, D. 759: "Unfinished" Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): C. A. Spina Plate Number: C. S. 19, 138, undated (Box 64, Folder 820)
  - Composer: Schuler, Adalbert Title: Der Schafer Uniform Title: Schafer Publisher information: New York: Luckhardt & Belder Plate Number: L. & B. 3567, undated (Box 174, Folder 3197)
  - Composer: Schuler, Adalbert Title: Der Sterbende Soldat Uniform Title: Sterbende Soldat Publisher information: New York: Adalbert Schuler, undated (Box 154, Folder 2344)
  - Composer: Schuler, Adalbert Title: Die Wasserrose Uniform Title: Wasserrose Publisher information: New York: Adalbert Schuler, undated (Box 154, Folder 2363)
  - Composer: Schuler, Adalbert Title: Gefunden Uniform Title: Gefunden Publisher information: New York: Adalbert Schuler, undated (Box 156, Folder 2441)
  - Composer: Schuler, Adalbert Title: Gleich und Gleich Uniform Title: Gleich und Gleich Publisher information: New York: Adalbert Schuler, undated (Box 156, Folder 2442)
  - Composer: Schuler, Adalbert Title: Gott grusse Dich! Uniform Title: Gott grusse Dich! Publisher information: New York: A. Schuler, undated (Box 153, Folder 2337)